<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KovenSoft</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_solutions">SolutionsActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Mobile Solutions</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Network Soluiotns</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Enterprise Solutions</string>
    <string name="text_mobile">Mobile Solutions:</string>
    <string name="mobile_image_content_description">Mobile Solutions</string>
    <string name="mobile_description">No matter what your mobile dreams are, Kovensoft can make them come true.
        We understand the complex usability issues that are involved in mobile sites and applications,
        as well as the need for a consistent brand across platforms.
        Our mobile solutions consultants can help you take your Mobile business.
        We can formulate and execute a cost-effective strategy for your mobile solution that
        includes compatibility between mobile browsers, devices and platforms,
        optimized usability and real-time integration with CMS, ERP, CRM,
        Payment Gateways or any kind of existing / new Backend System.</string>
    <string name="title_network">Network Solutions :</string>
    <string name="image_network_description">Network Solutions</string>
    <string name="description_network">As the data center environment expands, companies must find new ways to improve efficiency.
        To increase performance and improve the availability of data management networks,
        enterprises are migrating the overall system configuration from the traditional direct server-to-storage
        connection to a switched shared server-to-storage connection via fiber-optic cabling.
Networks are the backbone of your business and periodic evaluation is
        critical to accommodate new applications and to keep pace with business requirements.
        In today's business environment, enabling your network to work with multiple communication channels is paramount.
        Green IT offers design, integration and management services for customers who require flexible,
        robust and resilient network infrastructures. Our end-to-end network integration solutions help
        customers with complex network upgrades and mergers, expansions, or new deployments involving routers,
        switches, Firewalls, servers, and other network equipment.\n </string>
    <string name="description_network1">NET OPTIMIZATION SOLUTION\nSCALABILITY\nAVAILABILITY\nSECURITY\nPERFORMANCE</string>


</resources>
